

Mateusz Lota

Junior Tester (Trainee)



Poland, Łódź





+48 510 817 777

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mateusz-lota

GitHub:

https://github.com/Mateuszl.ota

SUMMARY:

I have a great desire and motivation to start a career in Testing industry. Thanks to technical education and past experience, I have the skills of being meticulous and inquisitive.

I know how to work with a lot of tasks and have good time management skills.

I'm fond of mountain biking and also material arts, I take part in amateur competitions. Reaching my goal despite any difficulties, I like learning something new and develop my skills, both personal and professional.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

IT SUPPORT

KONCEPT SYSTEMY INFORMATYCZNE S.C. | Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

- Remote users support.
- Installation and configuration of operating systems.
- Configuration of routers and servers.
- Solving urgent problems.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

DECATHLON | Sept 2021 - Mar 2022

- Assembling and repairing bikes.
- Customer service and advice.
- Maintaining a clean workplace.
- Solving urgent

EDUCATION:

UDEMY | Fundamentals of manual software testing Course

Jan 2022

Credential URL: Certificate Link

UDEMY | Certified Tester ISTQB® Foundation Level (CTFL) Updated 2022 Course

Jan 2022

Credential URL: Certificate Link

GEODETIC AND TECHNICAL SCHOOLS IN LODZ:

Vocational secondary school | 2017 - 2021

- IT technician
- EE08 Certificate.
- EE09 Certificate.

MAIN SKILLS:

Basic of: HTML, CSS

Basic of: JAVA

Basic of: SQL

Qtest, TestLink, Jira

- Basic ISTQB knowledge
- · Creating test cases and test scenarios
- · Basic of: Postman, SoapUI, API
- Making test plans
- Spanish A1
- English B2

Lagree to the processing of personal data provided in this obcument for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of ratural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation). I onsent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose necessary for the recruitment process (in accordancewith the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws of 2018, Item 1000) and in accordance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of Individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (RODO).